(Amy:)I think you'd be smart
enough to see that, too.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry I gave you such a hard
time, I just had to be sure.
(Raj:)It's pretty exciting that NASA
wants to send Howard back up.
(Bermadette:)Yeah, exciting.
(Bermadette:)Can I ask you something?
(Penny:)Course.
(Bernadette:)He hated that entire experience.
(Bernadette:)Does it make me an awful wife
(Bernadette:)if I don't think he
should do it again?
(Raj:)Not at all.
(Raj:)He's forgotten how miserable he was
the entire time he was up there.
(Raj:)It's like me in those moments
when I miss India.
(Bernadette:)So you'll talk to him?
(Raj:)Why me?
(Bernadette:)I'm his wife,
I don't want to ruin it for him.
(Raj:)That's the dynamic. I'm the
fun one, you're the buzzkill.
(Bernadette:)Since when am I the buzzkill?
(Raj:)-Do you think this is cool?
-No, I think it's stupid.
Aha!
(Bernadette:)You're right, it's great.